https://www.ridelow.co.uk/privacy-notice

Sales & Advice:
0161 834 5788 / 0161 831 9782
Over 1 Million Happy Customers
Opening Hours:
Bikes
Men's BikesRoad BikesMountain BikesHybrid BikesFixed Gear Bikes - FixiesTouring BikesElectric BikesTriathlonFolding BikesCruiser BikesTraditional BikesBMX BikesTricyclesLowrider BikesTandem BikesWomen's BikesRoad BikesMountain BikesHybrid BikesFolding BikesTraditional BikesBMX BikesCruiser BikesElectric BikesTricyclesChildren's BikesKIds BMX BikesTricyclesKIds Road BikesKids Balance BikesKids Cruiser BikesKids Traditional Bikes
Parts & Accessories
Bicycle BagsBicycle Baskets & CratesBicycle BellsBicycle Coffee HolderBicycle GlovesBicycle GripsBicycle HandlebarsHandlebar AccessoriesBicycle HelmetsBicycle HornsBicycle KickstandsBicycle LightsBicycle Locks and ChainsBicycle MirrorsBicycle MudguardsPannier Bags & LuggageBicycle Pannier RacksBicycle PedalsBicycle Seats and SaddlesBicycle Seat PostsBicycle StickersBicycle Surf RackBicycle Tyres & InnertubesBicycle Valve Caps
Brands
BernCharge BikesChrome BagsBackpacksMessenger BagsCamera BagsLaptop BagsSeat & Handlebar BagsTravel BagsSling BagsRolltop BagsCremeCubeDahonDiamondbackElectraExtremeGhostGT BikesKryptoniteLezyne LightsMafiaBikesMongoose BMXNew EraNS bikesNutcasePashleyProject 346RagleyRaleighRuff CyclesSE BikesSteco
Clearance
Contact Us
0My cart(0)
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Subtotal: £0.00
Account
My Account
My Cart
Checkout
Log In
Search:
Search
COVID-19 UPDATE: Free home delivery is still available - Read More
Home
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
Ridelow Privacy Policy.
Your privacy should be important to you, and it is very important to us. This notice explains our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.
What We Collect:
This applies to all information which is collected or submitted within the Ridelow website. On some pages, you can order products/subscriptions, make requests, and create an account with us. The types of personal information collected at these pages include Name, Address, Email Address, Phone Number, Payment Method and Billing Information.
The Way We Use Information:
We may collect information about your visit to the website. This is done anonymously and is used to help us measure activity in general on the site and it also helps us to come up with ideas to further improve the site and the service it provides. We automatically collect statistical data about usage patterns on our website. This information is not used to identify any individual. It is only collected to provide us with an understanding of the areas of interest on our site and kept only for as long as required for this purpose.
Any information we do collect is strictly for our use, and under no circumstances will we allow other companies access to this information.
The Ridelow web site may make use of "cookie" technology to measure site activity and to customize information to your personal tastes. A cookie is an element of data that a web site can send to your browser, which may then store the cookie on your hard drive. So, when you come back to visit us again, we can tailor information to suit your individual preferences. The goal is to save you time and provide you with a more meaningful visit.
Online privacy is taken seriously. It is our way of keeping your trust in Ridelow and our products and services that we provide. Ridelow reserves the right to alter our privacy principles as business needs require. Any alterations to these principles will be posted on our web site in a timely manner.
You also have the right to unsubscribe from our newsletter at any time by using the unsubscribe facility in our broadcasts or by requesting that we remove/unsubscribe you by emailing us at info@ridelow.co.uk
How You Can Access Or Correct Your Account Information:
You are able to modify your personally identifiable information by logging into the Ridelow online store using the username and password that you chose when you registered on the Ridelow web site. It is therefore your responsibility to keep this information accurate and up to date. Any problems arising from inaccurate information in your details may result in extra costs or delays in delivery. You have the right to contact us in order to remove consent, to correct, amend, or to erase your personal data at any time, where relevant. Where your information is required for statutory record keeping purposes, we reserve the right under UK Data Protection law not to comply with your request.
How To Contact Us:
Should you want to contact us with regards to any of our policies, or have other questions or concerns about the service Ridelow provides, please email info@ridelow.co.uk.
My Cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.
© 2020 Licence To Thrill Ltd. All Rights Reserved.
